Nicole Mazzuca

nicole@strega-nil.co | (425) 443-3734

ABOUT ME

I'm a local of Seattle, an urbanism, transit, and active transportation advocate. I love working on things of a mechanical nature, and have worked on my own bikes, as well as those of my family and friends, for years. I'm not a professional bike mechanic, but I have done everything from converting my old brompton to electric, to replacing brakes, to switching out chainrings.

EDUCATION

B.Sc. in Mathematics Western Washington University January 2018 - December 2019 Associate of Art Bellevue College September 2014 - July 2016

EXPERIENCE

Uptown Espresso - Barista

January 2024 -

- Interacting with customers while multitasking
- Much of the time, I'm alone on the job, meaning I take orders, make coffee, and handle the POS system for multiple customers at once.

Microsoft - Software Engineer

January 2020 - December 2023

- Worked on the foundational set of tools for programming on Windows
- Public facing role:
- Communicating with customers
- Figuring out customer requirements, and solving their problems
- Worked with people from German universities, Windows, Office, and even the US Air Force
- Supporting community helping run a community forum for 9000 people

Aegis Living, Issaquah - Maintenance

July 2014 - September 2016

- · General plumbing and electrical maintenance for retirement community
- Helped support community operations by doing lock maintenance, painting, and other miscellaneous tasks

SKILLS

- Espresso drinks on a semi-automatic machine
- · Milk microfoam with latte art
- Proper matcha preparation

Last updated May 29, 2024